

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Details

Flat 4, 26/f, Yuen Lam House, Block B, Hong Lam Court, Sha

Tin

Hong Kong +852 68902147

tony.f.liang@outlook.com

κil	

Python	
JavaScript	
С	
C#	
React.js	
Node.js	
Django	
SQL Server	
MongoDB	
Redis	
Microsoft Azure	

Links

github

Hobbies

Yoga, Reading, and Travelling

Profile

Having been self-learning programming extensively for a year, I have become a web developer in a Canadian IT consultancy based in Hong Kong for two years. To enhance my expertise, I have been taking various industry-related courses online and earned professional certifications after work.

Education

Biochemistry, The Hong Kong University Of Science And Technology, -Hong Kong

SEPTEMBER 2005 - JUNE 2009

Second Class Honor, Division 1

Dean's List in 2007-08 Fall

Employment History

Full-Stack Web Developer, Qualicom Innovations (Asia) Limited , Hong Kong

JULY 2019 - PRESENT

Representative Project Experience:

- 1. HSBC's VisionGo (07/2019-07/2020)
 - joined an agile team developing this global bank commercial client communication platform as a full stack developer
 - built the Nodejs Reactjs Azure-based web system, and related test suite
- 2. Cathay Pacific's Air Cargo Terminal Operator Job Assignment Optimization System (08/2020 present)
 - joined the system team developing the web-application module of the project as a full-stack developer
 - · built the Django Reactjs web system, and related test suite

General Manager, EQIHub, ShenZhen

DECEMBER 2014 - JULY 2018

- Co-founder of Eqihub, a co-working space and fin-tech platform in Shenzhen,
 China.
- organizing the early construction, building up working-team and the sequence operation management

Team Manager, AIA Group Limited, Hong Kong

MAY 2012 - NOVEMBER 2014

- Joined AIA as a financial planner in Hong Kong
- became Unit Manager in 2012, managing a team of ten insurance agents

General Manager, StudyCo, Hong Kong

DECEMBER 2009 - DECEMBER 2010

- Co-founder of StudyCo, an English Learning Center in Hong Kong,
- managing human resource and sales

Professional qualification and Certificate

Microsoft Certified: Azure Developer Associate

DECEMBER 2020

FreeCodeCamp.org Certified Developer

Specialized in:

- 1. Responsive Web Design developer
- 2. Javascript Algorithms And Data Structures Developer

Relevant Vocational Training

Online Courses

NOVEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

- Coursera
 - 1. Neural Networks and Deep Learning, Grade of 97.9%
- MongoDB University
 - 1. M103: Basic Cluster Administration, Grade of 92%
 - 2. M121: The MongoDB Aggregation Framework, Grade of 93%
- Redis University
 - 1. RU101: Introduction to Redis Data Structures, Grade of 75%
 - 2. RU202: Redis Streams, Grade of 93%
- Udemy
 - 1. Server-Side Rendering with React and Redux
 - 2. Node JS: Advanced Concepts
 - 3. C Programming For Beginners Master the C Language
 - 4. React The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)
 - 5. The Complete Node.js Developer Course (3rd Edition)

Volunteer Service and Charity

- The president of the student union of Hong Kong Tang King Po College(HKTKPC) in 2004
- Advocate and annual donor of HKTKPC Alumni Scholarship Fund